Breathing exercises. Different languages have different breathing patterns. Because
Americans are a little louder than you may expect, in order to emulate this
projection of the voice, you're going to have to take deeper breaths than you're
accustomed to. Stand up straight, chest out, inhale deeply, and in a deep voice
say, hi, how's it going? As you saw with phrasing, your breathing should be in sync
with the phrasing and punctuation. If you're saying something short, you can get
away with a more shallow inhale, but short panting breaths are interpreted as nervous
or impatient, whereas long, deep exhalations of sound are considered calm
and confident. Take deeper breaths than usual and push the sound out from deep in
your chest. Pay particular attention that you do not push the air out through your
nose, which would create a very unattractive nasal quality to your speech.